When we look at log returns of a stock,
在查看股票的对数收益率时
we assume that the previous period's value gives us
我们假定上个时期的值
some insight into the next period's value.
能够从某种程度上体现下个时期的值
It's also reasonable to assume that the past couple of
还可以假定前几天的数据点
data points give us hints as to what the next value will be.
可以暗示下个值将是什么
This is the main principle behind Auto-regressive Models.
这是自回归模型的主要原则
An autoregressive model, also called an AR model,
自回归模型（AR 模型）
tries to fit a line that is a linear combination of previous values.
尝试用一条线拟合以前值的线性组合
The AR model includes an Intercept which represents
AR 模型包含一个截距
some constant that is independent of the previous values.
表示某个常量 它不受以前值的影响
The AR model also includes an Error term,
AR 模型还包含一个误差项
which represents movements that cannot be predicted using the previous values.
表示无法使用以前的值预测的变化
Let's see how we prepare the time-series data,
我们来看看如何准备时序数据
to feed it into an Autoregressive model.
并将数据传入自回归模型中
As an example, our AR model will use
作为示例 我们的 AR 模型将使用
the previous two values to predict the current value.
前两个值预测当前值
For example, if we have daily data for Monday, Tuesday,
例如 假设我们有周一 周二和周三的每日数据
and Wednesday, then we use Monday and Tuesday as the independent variables.
使用周一和周二作为自变量
We also define Wednesday as the dependent variable that the Model tries to predict.
并将周三设为模型要预测的因变量
Then, when we move on to Thursday,
然后分析周四的值
we use the previous two days to predict Thursday's value.
我们使用前两天的值预测周四的值
If data from a previous period has some predictive value,
如果上一个时期的数据具有预测值
then this coefficient will be non-zero.
那么这个系数不为零
The number of past values used in the model is known as the Lag.
模型中使用的历史值数量称为 Lag
We define an AR model by its Lag.
我们用 Lag 定义 AR 模型
For example, a model that only uses yesterday's value and ignores the rest,
例如 如果模型仅使用昨天的值并忽略剩余的值
is an AR 1 Model.
则称为 AR 1 模型
Whereas, a model that uses
如果模型
the two previous days' values and ignores the rest is an AR 2 Model,
使用前两天的值并忽略剩余的值 则称为 AR 2 模型
the previous three days' values and ignores the rest is an AR 3 Model.
使用前三天的值并忽略剩余的值 则称为 AR 3 模型
We write Auto-regressive Models as ARP,
我们将自回归模型表示为 AR(p)
where p stands for the lag.
p 表示 lag
We can choose different lag values to train
我们可以使用不同的滞后值训练模型
your model and see how they perform on test data.
看看模型在测试数据上的表现
We can check if the coefficients are significantly different from zero.
例如查看系数是否与零相差很大
If some coefficients are likely zero,
如果某些系数可能为零
then you can reduce the lag and focus the model on the more recent values.
那么可以降低滞后值 并让模型侧重于更近期的值
As with any regression model,
与任何回归模型一样
you can also check the adjusted R squared to get a sense of how
你还可以查看调整后的 R^2
well the independent variables explain the movements of the dependent variables.
看看自变量对因变量的变化解释效果如何
Note that an AR model is designed to represent a single time series.
注意 AR 模型专门表示单个时序
If you have several different time series,
如果有多个不同的时序
you could build a separate AR model for each.
可以为每个时序构建单独的 AR 模型
But what if the movement of one stock has some relation to the movement of another?
但是如果一支股票的变化与另一支的变化有联系呢？
You may be seeing something similar with multivariate multiple regression.
你可能在多变量多元回归中见过类似的情形
To account for interdependence among more than one time series,
要考虑多个时序之间的联系
we can use the multivariate version of autoregression.
我们可以使用多变量形式的自回归
This is called a vector autoregressive model.
称为向量自回归模型
Note that having some familiarity with
注意 在后面学习配对交易时
the vector autoregressive model will help you
熟悉向量自回归模型
as you learn about pairs trading in a later lesson.
将对你有帮助